In this video, we will learn how to make a pumpkin skirt.
First, we first freeze the belt, and then delete the excess outer layer, that is, the outer layer of the cake skirt.
Only keep the inner layer.
After simple simulation, we select the bottom and add elasticity to the bottom, it will automatically close.
After closing, we can reduce the proportion a little bit to check if it is tight.
After tightening, it looks like a pumpkin skirt.
Then we can select these plates to add pressure to it.
Because the bottom is tight, so you add pressure.
Then it will hold up.
After holding up, it will look more obvious, more like a pumpkin skirt.
If you feel that the pressure is too obvious when it is 2, you can adjust the pressure to 0.5.
Click on the triangle on the left to reduce the pressure.
Because we use elasticity, so now the bottom of our skirt is fixed.
It can't move up or down.
Many times,
the bottom of the skirt we see may be more obvious.
So we have to adjust it.
Then here we can cancel the elasticity first.
Then the anti-activated outer layer of the plate.
We first fix the fixed belt in the bottom of the skirt.
First, change to the rectangular tool.
In the position we think is appropriate.
For example, now I click on it.
I think this position is about the same.
Just around this tight position.
To create an almost 3 times wider leg or 2.5 times wider rectangle.
Then create a symmetrical plate.
Continue to select these two plates at the same time.
After selecting a plate, click on Shift again to select more.
Then press Shift F to open the arrangement point.
Arrange them in the front position.
Then adjust the diameter.
Then you can close the arrangement point.
If the arrangement position is a little cross.
Or if you need to adjust it.
We will manually use the positioning ball to adjust it.
After arranging, use the satin sewing machine to sew the two ends together.
Then because the whole plate is relatively small.
Here we can click on the display grid to see.
The number of grid is very small.
So the sewing line in the middle is not very dense.
There are only two sewing lines.
So before we can start the simulation.
Reduce the particle diameter of the plate to 10.
Reduce the conflict thickness to 1.
After starting the simulation, the plate will fall down.
Press Ctrl Z to return to the previous.
Before we start the simulation.
We can press W and click the plate.
The position we click will create a fixed pin.
Then press W and click the pin.
You can delete the fixed pin.
Then we can use the satin sewing machine.
Fixed to the virtual model.
This function.
A point of the plate is fixed to the virtual model.
When you click.
Be sure to pay attention to the angle.
As much as possible.
We add a satin sewing machine.
It's really parallel.
Or when we add a satin sewing machine.
Don't go too far.
Then we can narrow some plates.
After narrowing the plate.
We basically have this plate.
It can now be fixed.
In the position near our thigh.
If we add a sewing needle.
If it's not very symmetrical.
You can use the satin sewing machine.
To adjust the position of the point on the model.
At this time.
Be sure to pay attention to the point in the selection.
It's a red dot.
That is, the point on the virtual model.
Now.
The whole panel is tight.
It's on the human body.
We can manually drag the panel.
Let it be fixed.
In a more flat position.
Then we apply a new fabric to these two panels.
Increase the friction coefficient of the new fabric.
This can prevent the fabric from sliding.
After adjusting the friction coefficient.
We can drag a panel to see.
When we drag a panel.
It's like there's a lot of friction.
Fix it there.
There will be no mutual sliding.
The advantage of doing this is.
After us.
For example, some changes.
Or if you record an animation.
Can prevent.
Because the movement of the legs is relatively large.
Affect.
If this edge is visible.
You put the bottom of the skirt.
Sew to the top of this edge.
If you want to make it invisible.
You sew it under this edge.
Or apply a transparency to this edge.
All right.
Here.
I use the line sewing tool.
Sew it directly on this edge.
Because this edge.
The position we do.
It's more natural than it is.
Is to lean on it.
So after we start the simulation.
Will see.
The effect of his pumpkin.
It will be more obvious.
A little better.
After completion.
You can.
According to the need.
To reduce the particle diameter.
Or change the fabric properties.
And pressure.